<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SemesterProject</string>
    <string name="title_activity_math_content">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_textRatio">
        "<b>Ratio</b>\n\n"

        "In mathematics, a ratio indicates how many times one number contains another. For example, if there are eight oranges and six lemons in a bowl of fruit, then the ratio of oranges to lemons is eight to six (that is, 8∶6, which is equivalent to the ratio 4∶3). Similarly, the ratio of lemons to oranges is 6∶8 (or 3∶4) and the ratio of oranges to the total amount of fruit is 8∶14 (or 4∶7).\n"
        "The numbers in a ratio may be quantities of any kind, such as counts of people or objects, or such as measurements of lengths, weights, time, etc. In most contexts, both numbers are restricted to be positive.\n"
        "A ratio may be specified either by giving both constituting numbers, written as "a to b" or "a∶b",or by giving just the value of their quotient a/b. Equal quotients correspond to equal ratios.\n"
        "Consequently, a ratio may be considered as an ordered pair of numbers, a fraction with the first number in the numerator and the second in the denominator, or as the value denoted by this fraction. Ratios of counts, given by (non-zero) natural numbers, are rational numbers, and may sometimes be natural numbers. When two quantities are measured with the same unit, as is often the case, their ratio is a dimensionless number. A quotient of two quantities that are measured with different units is called a rate.\n"
        "<b>Notation and terminology</b>\n\n"
        "The ratio of numbers A and B can be expressed as: \n"
        "-the ratio of A to B\n"
        "-A∶B\n"
        "-A is to B (when followed by "as C is to D "; see below)\n"
        "a fraction with A as numerator and B as denominator that represents the quotient (i.e., A divided by B or A/B). This can be expressed as a simple or a decimal fraction, or as a percentage, etc.\n"

        "The numbers A and B are sometimes called terms of the ratio, with A being the antecedent and B being the consequent.\n"

        "A statement expressing the equality of two ratios A∶B and C∶D is called a proportion, written as A∶B = C∶D or A∶B:C∶D. This latter form, when spoken or written in the English language, is often expressed as\n "
        "(A is to B) as (C is to D). "
        "A, B, C and D are called the terms of the proportion. A and D are called its extremes, and B and C are called its means. The equality of three or more ratios, like A∶B = C∶D = E∶F, is called a <b>continued proportion.</b>\n "
        "Ratios are sometimes used with three or even more terms, e.g., the proportion for the edge lengths of a <b>Examples</b> that is ten inches long is therefore\n"
        "thickness : width : length =2:4:10\n"
        "The meaning of such a proportion of ratios with more than two terms is that the ratio of any two terms on the left-hand side is equal to the ratio of the corresponding two terms on the right-hand side. "
        "<b>Big Foot Example</b>\n\n"
        "A Recipe for pancakes uses 3 cups of flour and 2 cups of milk.\n"
        "So the ratio of flour to milk is 3 : 2\n"
        "To make pancakes for a LOT of people we might need 4 times the quantity, so we multiply the numbers by 4:\n"
        "3×4 : 2×4 = 12 : 8\n"
        "In other words, 12 cups of flour and 8 cups of milk.\n"
        "<i>two by four</i>"
        "Allie measured her foot and it was 21cm long, and then she measured her Mother\'s foot, and it was 24cm long.\n "
        "But then she thought to measure heights, and found she is 133cm tall, and her Mom is 152cm tall.\n"

        "The foot-to-height ratio in fraction style is:\n"
        "Allie:	 21/133 and Mom: 24/152\n"
        "So the ratio for Allie is 21 : 133\n "
        "By dividing both values by 7 we get 21/7 : 133/7 = 3 : 19 \n"
        "It is still the same ratio, right? Because we divided both numbers by the same amount.\nAnd the ratio for Mom is 24 : 152\n "
        "By dividing both values by 8 we get 24/8 : 152/8 = 3 : 19\n"
        "This time we divided by 8, but that ratio stays the same, too.\nThe simplified foot-to-height ratios are now:\nAllie:	 3/19 	 	Mom:	 3/19"


    </string>
    <string name="large_textRate">
        "A ratio is a comparison of two numbers or measurements. The numbers or measurements being compared are called the terms of the ratio."

    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ratio_content_page">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_math_rates_content">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling_rates">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
</resources>